[Music]
What in life better
provides instant
pleasure and happ
food here some houses
are buy with K the
process of preparing
large quan of K
before winter
[Music] As
autumn is approaching the latter half of the year,
kimchi season is approaching. Usually, when we say kimchi
set meal, it means
kimchi including vegetables
and spes used
make index for the
year and hence the entire
Nation gets
busy making
KCH a process that
varies according to
the topography and
climate of each
region the history
of mankind is all
about human efforts
to adapt to nature
win in are prepared
seas when Spring
fishermen go
out to sea to catch
shrimps and various
types of fish which
are fermented and
used to enrich the
flavor of
Kim salt Essential
for preserved
vegetables is
produced by salt
farmers toil away
under the blazing
sun all summer
long Chili pepper
brought to Korea 460
years ago has become
a key spicy
ingredient and IS
prepared in late
fall and napa
cabbage fully grown
in early winter
signaling that All
is ready for
K these are the
natural ingredients
used to make
KCI to get through
winter when fresh
feses are hard to
come by Koreans  have
been making kimch
[Music]
[Music] It is
hard, but I also feel
proud that I did something for my family, and
there is a special taste to it, you know, the taste of kimchi. The fact that
this passes down our family's
flavor to our children from generation to generation—that is why I
bring my daughter-in-law along and do this kimchi-making.
Kim has been
kept alive as an internal
means of
[Music]
subsist ID
not,
but research shows
that 94% of Koreans eat katsu. Aes
in Korea have consisted
of a bowl
of rice soup and an array of side dishes, all of which are served at once. One of them is KCI. There are as many as different variations over time. People began to embrace
the concept
of
convenience in their
daily
lives. Today, one can easily find fresh vegetables in winter and buy ready-made
kimchi all year round. Long
for Koreans. However, it has become a
ritual to make kimchi at
home when the season comes. This also holds true for many Korean families living abroad. [Music] [Music] However, for our country, I think kimchi-making is a deep sense of sentiment passed down from mother to grandmother to grandmother after that, in every household.
December has arrived. And at kindergarten, special kimchi-making
takes
education from their
kindergarten.
To help you become a little more familiar with kimchi, and also,
after making it, the children feel a
sense of pride knowing they made it; they
eat kimchi better because of this.
[Music]
[Music] [Music] It is
Kimjang season.
Hello. We are [doing] this. If
you have time, please
[Music] help us.
Kimjang season
[Applause]
Kimjang is a labor-intensive process, so
residents share the
burden of labor by
helping each
household with their
Kim during this time.
As
well as relatives
and neighbors, join in to make the
large quantity of Kimchi
this time, both
men and women work
together.
[Music]
By having the whole family work together to make this Kimjang, a spirit of cooperation and collaboration is
fostered, and I think that love is also
created among family members.
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
underground,
following the
traditional way, this
kimchi will ripen
through the magical
process of
[Music]
fermentation. Kimjang and
Kimchi culture are
deeply rooted in
the lives of Korean
people and can be enjoyed fresh, thanks to
all
improved
refrigeration and
fermentation techniques, including
making and storing
kimch has become an
inseparable of
Koreans
lives Just Like
always the mother
takes out some kimch
that made last
winter from the
Kimchi
refrigerator and
plates of different
Kimchi are served
completing an
enjoyable meal for
this family There
are countless ways
of storing
vegetables among
[Music]
Kim Tae-geuk west
comm chore
[Music]
Kimjang is
tests use
Nature de culture
beed the future
generations AS symb
of sharing and
communicating
cultural
[Music]
heritage l